Guide to the Records of the Student Senators Council RG.44.0.1
New York University Archives
- Series I: Administrative Files, 1974-2016; 13.73 Linear Feet in 27 manuscript boxes and 3 oversized shared flat boxes
  - Committee Preference and Description Student Body Alternatives, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - General Information, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Office of Student Activities (OSA), 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Packet Originals, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Religious Holidays, Univ. Policy, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Sample Packets, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Washington Square News, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Calendar of Meetings, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Committee Description, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Committee Description: Senate, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - General Info Sheet/Organization Chart, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Religious Holidays, University Policy, 1998-1999 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Sample Packets, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Handbook - New York University, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Calendar of Meetings, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Code of Conduct, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Committee Description, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Committee Description: Senate, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Committee Preference & Description (Student Body), 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Packet Originals, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Religious Holidays, University Policy, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Calendar Of Meetings (SSC & UCSL versions), 2000-2001 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Committee Description: Senate, 2000-2001 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Committee Description: SSC/UCSL, 2000-2001 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Flier Distribution (Deans), 2000-2001 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Grievance Material (RESTRICTED), 2000-2001 (Box 159, Folder 12)
  - Inquiries from the Student Body, 2000-2001 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Kimmel Center, 2000-2001 (Box Shared University Archives 145, Folder 11)
  - Religious Holidays: University Policy, 2000-2001 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Sample Packets, 2000-2001 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Administrative Papers, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Calendar of Meetings (SSC & UCSL versions), 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Committee Description: Senate, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Committee Description: SSC/UCSL, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Committee Preference and Description (Student Body/Alternates), 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Flier Distribution Labels, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Information Sent to SSC/UCSL, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - NYU T-Shirts, 2001-2002 (Box Shared University Archives 097, Folder 4)
  - Packet Samples, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Purpose and Status: UCSL, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Religious Holidays: University Policy, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Space, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Administrative/Faculty Handbook, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Calendar of Meetings: SSC, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Calendar of Meetings: UCSL, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Committee Descriptions: Senate, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Committee Descriptions: SSC/UCSL, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - In Memoriam, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Inquiries from the Student Body, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Meeting Materials, 2002, 2004, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Office of Student Activities (Orientation), 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Packet Samples, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Presidential Challenge Fund, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Presidential Installation, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 11-12)
  - Presidential Service Awards, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Questions for Senate, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Religious Holidays, University Policy, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Search Committee: VP for Student Affairs, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Town Hall Meetings, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Washington Square News, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - World Trade Center, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Beginning, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Calendar of Meetings: SSC, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Calendar of Meetings: UCSL, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Challenge Fund, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Class Council, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Committee Description: Senate, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Committee Description: SSC/UCSL, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Committee Preference and Description (Student Body/Alternates), 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Committee Summaries, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Committee Summaries (SSC, UCSL, Student Body), 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Commuter Students, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Deans, Directors, Admins, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - General Information, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - In Memoriam, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Label List, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Meeting Materials, 2003-2005 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Meetings with the President, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Packet Originals, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Packet Samples, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Presidential Service Awards, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Questions for Senate, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Religious Holidays, University Policy, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Ruth Pengas' Email Correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 7-8)
  - Ruth Pengas Materials (Administration), 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Student Guest Speakers, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Washington Square News, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Admin/Dean/Directors, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Administrative Files, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Calendar of Meetings: SSC, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Calendar of Meetings: UCSL, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Challenge Fund/Senior Class Legacy, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Committee Description: Senate, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Committee Description: SSC/USCL, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Committee Preference and Description (Student Body), 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Communication Hospitality, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Coordinated Election Period, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Enterprise Communications, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - In Memoriam, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Meeting Materials, 2004-2006 (Box 19, Folder 20, Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Meetings with the President, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Orientation, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Packet Originals, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Packet Samples, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Program Board, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Round Tables, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Transparencies, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Zuckerman Forum, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Calendar of Meetings: SSC, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Calendar of Meetings: UCSL, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Commencement, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Committee Preference and Description (Student Body), 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Communication/Hospitality Outreach, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Distinguished Teachers, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Enterprise Communications, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - External Affairs/Albany Day, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Hospitality Outreach, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Meetings with the President, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Office of Student Activities, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Packet Originals, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Packet Samples, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Religious Holidays, University Policy, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Calendar of Meetings: SSC, 2006-2007 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Commuter Students, 2006-2007 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Labels, 2006-2007 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Meetings with the President, 2006-2007 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Office of Student Activities, 2006-2007 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Student Faculty Relations, 2006-2007 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Town Halls/Forums/Soap Box, 2006-2007 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Abu Dhabi, 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Calendar of Meetings: SSC, 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Calendar of Meetings: UCSL, 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Coca-Cola, 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Commencement, 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Forum, 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - General Forms, 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Information Technology Services (ITS), 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Inquiries from the Student Body, 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Lotterized Dinners - Student Roundtables, 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Office of Student Activities, 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Packet Originals, 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Polytechnic Institute, 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Senate Packets, 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Student Services, 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Survey Sample, 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Town Hall Meetings, 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Summer Months Task Overview, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Calendar of Meetings: SSC, 2008-2009 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Calendar of Meetings: UCSL, 2008-2009 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Committee Descriptions: SSC/UCSL, 2008-2009 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Committee Preference and Description (Student Body & Alternates), 2008-2009 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Distinguished Teachers/Distinguished Administrators, 2008-2009 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - External Affairs/Albany Day, 2008-2009 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Kimmel Protest, 2008-2009 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Meeting Materials, 2008-2009 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Middle States, 2008-2009 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - New York Minute, 2008-2009 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Office of Student Activities, 2008-2009 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Orientation, 2008-2009 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Packet Samples, 2008-2009 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Portfolio, 2008-2009 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Student (Undergraduate & Graduate) Dinners with President, 2008-2009 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Town Halls/Forums/Soap Box, 2008-2009 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Washington Square News, 2008-2009 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Administrative, 2009-2010 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Administrative Papers, 2009-2010 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Meeting Materials, 2009-2013 (Box 22, Folder 12-13)
  - Secretary/E-Comm, 2011 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Student Government at NYU, 2011-2012 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Ecomm Archives, 2012-2014 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Meeting Materials, 2012-2013 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - 2013 Senators Binder (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Meeting Materials, 2013-2015 (Box 23, Folder 6-9)
  - Abolish the Box, 2013 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Operation of the University Bookstore (Barnes & Nobles), 2015 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - NYUSSC - Chair Binder (SSC/UCSL), 2015-2016 (Box 24, Folder 2-5, Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Restructure, 2015-2016 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Meeting Materials, 2016 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Member Certificate Templates, undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - RA Dorm Labels for Mailings, undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Series II: Committees and Boards, 1976-2015; 40.78 Linear Feet in 92 manuscript boxes and 1 half manuscript box
  Series II focuses upon the Student Senators Council's numerous committees relating to university life. Materials in this series consists mainly of meeting notes, memos, correspondence, reports, some audiocassette tapes, and administrative documents.
  The Student Senators Council (SSC) ran numerous committees that covered various aspects of university life. Each senator was expected to participate in these committees. Committees were divided between SSC Standing Committees and SSC Ad-Hoc Committees.
  The SSC Standing Committees are: (1) University Committee on Student Life Executive Committee: coordinates the activities of the SSC and its committees and subcommittees; (2) Student Grievance Committee: focuses upon disputes between student organizations, student or residence hall councils, and is responsible for supervising and administrating the SSC censure procedures; (3) Committee on Rules and Organization: reviews proposals to amend or adopt any Rules of Procedure of the SSC, the UCSL, and any of their committees, and periodically reviews the organizational policies of University student government.
  SSC Ad-Hoc Committee: Student Financial Aid and Compensation: Handles financial aid matters and works in conjunction with the Office of Financial Aid and the Office of Government Relations
  The University Committee on Student Life (UCSL) assists the SSC in areas related to students' extracurricular life and was divided into UCSL Standing Committees and UCSL Ad-Hoc Committees.
  UCSL Standing Committees: (1) Committee on Academic Services: handles matters concerning academically-related support services and programs provided by the University to students; (2) All Square Student Budget Allocation Committee (ASSBAC): establishes the criteria under which student organizations may receive All-Square funding, allocates such funding to student organizations, and monitors the use of allocated funds; (3) Committee on External Affair: considers all matters relating to the SSC/UCSL's association with external organizations; (4) Committee on Graduate Affairs: considers all matters relating to the academic and extracurricular life of students enrolled in the graduate and professional schools of the University; (5) Committee on Student Services: considers non-academic matters relating to the general well-being and comfort of the NYU students.
  Members of the Committee on Student Services are assigned to the following sub-committees: (a) Food Advisory Board: works with representatives from campus dining, deal with matters of food quality, and make recommendations; (b) Recreation Committee: deal with matters relating to the development of policy, facilities, and services at the Coles Sports Center.
  (6) Committee on Undergraduate Affairs: considers all matters that relate to the academic and extracurricular life of students enrolled in the undergraduate divisions and acts as a liaison among the different undergraduate student councils; (7) Inter Greek Council (IGC): represents the interests of and considering issues relating to fraternity and sorority life at the University; (8) Inter Residence Hall Council (IRHC): represents the interest of undergraduate students who reside in housing facilities which are owned or otherwise administered by the University and who are represented by a formal residence hall council, including fraternity and sorority housing facilities administered by the University. The committee also advices University officials on rules and policies related to residence halls.
  (9) Student Activities Board (SAB): oversees the life of student organizations registered with the Student Activities Office, establishes the necessary guidelines for forming an organization, and disputes involving student organizations; (10) Student Affairs Budget Advisory Committee (SABAC): deals with matters relating to the budget, policies, personnel, and practices of the Division of Student Affairs and Services.
  UCSL Ad-Hoc Committees: (1) Committee on Alumni Relations: considers issues concerning the relationship between current students and alumni; (2) Student Health Advisory Board: considers all matters relating to the University Health Center and shall take special interest in informing the student body about the services that the center provides
  The above information was taken from a document from the collection: Summary of the Committees of the Student Senators Council (SSC) and the SSC's University Committee on Student Life (UCSL), June 2004
  This series contains personal information that falls under the Federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA). This material is permanently restricted.
  - Review Committee on Student Affairs, 1976 (Box 241, Folder 5)
  - Minutes Committee on Student Life, 1976-1977 (Box 242, Folder 1)
  - Board of Communications, 1977 (Box 242, Folder 2)
  - Censure (RESTRICTED), 1977 (Box Shared University Archives 098, Audiocassette 44.0.1_0001 - 44.0.1_0003)
  - Subcommittee on All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC), 1977 (Box 242, Folder 4)
  - Subcommittee on All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC) Preliminary Report with Roster of Registered Organizations, 1977 (Box 242, Folder 5)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC), 1977-1978 (Box 242, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Housing, 1977-1978 (Box 242, Folder 7-8)
  - Independent Student Coalition, 1977-1978 (Box 243, Folder 1)
  - Public Affairs Committee - Athletics Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 243, Folder 2)
  - Publications Committee - Washington Square News, 1977-1978 (Box 243, Folder 3)
  - Security, 1977-1978 (Box 243, Folder 4)
  - Security Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 243, Folder 5)
  - Senate Committee to Advise on the Libraries, 1977-1978 (Box 243, Folder 6)
  - SSC, 1977-1978 (Box 243, Folder 7)
  - Student Activities Board, 1977-1978 (Box 243, Folder 8)
  - WSUC Student Council, 1977-1978 (Box 243, Folder 9)
  - Subcommittee to Review the Student Affairs Budget, 1977-1978 (Box 243, Folder 10)
  - Subcommittee on Space, 1977-1978 (Box 243, Folder 11)
  - University Judicial Board, 1977-1978 (Box 243, Folder 12)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC) Minutes, 1978 (Box 243, Folder 13)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Food, 1978-1979 (Box 243, Folder 14)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC), 1978-1979 (Box 243, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Council Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box Shared University Archives 098, Audiocassette 44.0.1_0005, Audiocassette 44.0.1_0008)
  - Publications Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 244, Folder 1)
  - Student Activities Board (SAB), 1978-1979 (Box 244, Folder 2)
  - Student Activities Budget Review Subcommittee - Minutes 11/27/1978, 1978-1979 (Box 244, Folder 3)
  - Student Affairs Budget Review Subcommittee, 1978-1979 (Box 244, Folder 4)
  - Student Senators Ad Hoc Committee On South Africa, 1978-1979 (Box 244, Folder 5)
  - Student Senators Security Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 244, Folder 6)
  - Student Senators University Judicial Board, 1978-1979 (Box 244, Folder 7)
  - University Committee On Student Life: Independent Student Coalition, 1978-1979 (Box 244, Folder 8)
  - Untitled Audiocassette Tapes, 1978-1979 (Box Shared University Archives 098, Audiocassette 44.0.1_0004, Audiocassette 44.0.1_0006 - 44.0.1_0007, Audiocassette 44.0.1_0009)
  - Academic Affairs, 1979-1980 (Box 244, Folder 9)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC), 1979-1980 (Box 244, Folder 10)
  - Financial Affairs Committee - Budget, 1979-1980 (Box 244, Folder 11)
  - Food Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 244, Folder 12)
  - Gay People's Union, 1979-1980 (Box 244, Folder 13)
  - Interfraternity Council, 1979-1980 (Box 244, Folder 14)
  - Public Affairs Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 245, Folder 1)
  - Recreation Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 245, Folder 2)
  - School Councils, 1979-1980 (Box 245, Folder 3)
  - Security Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 245, Folder 4)
  - Student Activities Board, 1979-1980 (Box 245, Folder 5)
  - Student Affairs Budget Advisory Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 245, Folder 6)
  - Academic Affairs, 1980-1981 (Box 245, Folder 7)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC), 1980-1981 (Box 245, Folder 8)
  - Elections Committee (Ad Hoc), 1980-1981 (Box 245, Folder 10)
  - Evening Students Facilities Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 245, Folder 11)
  - Faculty/Student Relations Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 245, Folder 12)
  - Food Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 246, Folder 1)
  - Gay People's Union, 1980-1981 (Box 246, Folder 2)
  - Housing Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 246, Folder 3)
  - Independent Student Coalition, 1980-1981 (Box 246, Folder 4)
  - Judicial Board, 1980-1981 (Box 246, Folder 5)
  - Public Affairs Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 246, Folder 6)
  - Recreation Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 246, Folder 7)
  - Security Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 246, Folder 9)
  - Student Activities Board (SAB), 1980-1981 (Box 246, Folder 10)
  - Student Affairs Budget Advisory, 1980-1981 (Box 246, Folder 11)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC) - General, 1981-1982 (Box 160, Folder 1-2)
  - Budget Advisory Committee (BAC), 1981-1982 (Box 160, Folder 3)
  - Coles Advisory Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 160, Folder 6)
  - Committee to Evaluate Student Activities Regulations (CESAR), 1981-1982 (Box 160, Folder 4-5)
  - Communications Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 160, Folder 7)
  - Food Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 160, Folder 8)
  - Gay People's Union, 1981-1982 (Box 160, Folder 9)
  - Night Students Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 246, Folder 12)
  - Program Board, 1981-1982 (Box 246, Folder 13)
  - Public Affairs Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 246, Folder 14)
  - Report: Committee On Sexual Assault, 1981-1982 (Box 160, Folder 10)
  - Space Usage Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 246, Folder 15)
  - Student Activities Board All-Square Status Guideline, 1981-1982 (Box 246, Folder 16)
  - Student Councils, 1981-1982 (Box 246, Folder 18)
  - Student/Faculty Relations Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 247, Folder 1)
  - Student Leaders (non-UCSL), 1981-1982 (Box 247, Folder 2)
  - Student Organizations: Registered, 1981-1982 (Box 247, Folder 3)
  - American Association of University Students, 1982 (Box 161, Folder 1)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 161, Folder 2)
  - Affirmative Action (Ad Hoc), 1982-1983 (Box 161, Folder 3)
  - Alcohol Task Force, 1982-1983 (Box 161, Folder 4)
  - American Association of University Students, 1982-1983 (Box 162, Folder 1)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC), 1982-1983 (Box 162, Folder 2)
  - Budget Advisory Committee (BAC), 1982-1983 (Box 162, Folder 3)
  - Coles Advisory Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 162, Folder 4)
  - Committee on the Libraries, 1982-1983 (Box 162, Folder 5)
  - Communications Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 162, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 162, Folder 7)
  - Financial Affairs Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 162, Folder 8)
  - Food Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 162, Folder 9)
  - Gay People's Union, 1982-1983 (Box 162, Folder 10)
  - Housing Committee, etc…, 1982-1983 (Box 162, Folder 11-12)
  - Independent Student Coalition, 1982-1983 (Box 162, Folder 13)
  - Judicial Board, 1982-1988 (Box 247, Folder 4)
  - Night Students Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 163, Folder 1)
  - New York Public Interest Research Group (NYPIRG), 1982-1983 (Box 163, Folder 2)
  - PAND, 1982-1983 (Box 163, Folder 3)
  - Public Affairs Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 163, Folder 4)
  - Recreation Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 163, Folder 5)
  - Registration Improvement Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 163, Folder 6)
  - Space Usage Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 163, Folder 7)
  - Student Activities Board (SAB), 1982-1983 (Box 163, Folder 8)
  - Student Senators Council (SSC)/All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC) - General, 1982-1983 (Box 161, Folder 5-8)
  - Summary of UCSL Committees, 1982-1983 (Box 163, Folder 9)
  - University Image Task Force, 1982-1983 (Box 163, Folder 10)
  - Grievance Committee, 1983 (Box 163, Folder 11)
  - American Association of University Students (AAUS), 1983-1984 (Box 163, Folder 12)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC), 1983-1984 (Box 163, Folder 13)
  - Coles Advisory Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 163, Folder 14)
  - Committee Preference Form, 1983-1984 (Box 163, Folder 15)
  - Dormitory Council, 1983-1984 (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 164, Folder 2)
  - Financial Affairs Committee (Senate), 1983-1984 (Box 247, Folder 5)
  - Housing Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 164, Folder 3)
  - Independent Student Coalition, 1983-1984 (Box 164, Folder 4)